A Guide to the Publications of the Bibliographical Society of the University of Virginia, 1947-1997
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Separate Publications
  - de Montluzin, Emily Lorraine. Attributions of Authorship in the Gentleman's Magazine, 1731-1868: A Supplement to Kuist. Charlottesville: Bibliographical Society of the University of Virginia, distributed electronically by University of Virginia Electronic Text Center, January 1997., 1997.1
    Searchable electronic database, encoded in TEI-conformant SGML, of accounts published in
    44 (1991), 45 (1992), 46 (1993), 47 (1994), 49 (1996), and 50 (1997). Encoding by David L. Gants and the University of Virginia Electronic Text Center.
  - Shakespearean Prompt-Books of the Seventeenth Century, ed. G. Blakemore Evans. Charlottesville: Bibliographical Society of the University of Virginia, distributed electronically by University of Virginia Electronic Text Center, March 1997., 1997.2
    Searchable electronic page facsimiles, encoded in TEI-conformant SGML, of the eight prompt-books published by the Society (1960.2, 1963.2, 1964.3, 1966.3, 1970.3, 1980.1, 1989.1, 1996.1). Scanning and proofing by the University of Virginia Electronic Text Center.
  - Studies in Bibliography, ed. Fredson Bowers, L. A. Beaurline, and David L. Vander Meulen. Charlottesville: Bibliographical Society of the University of Virginia, distributed electronically by University of Virginia Electronic Text Center, March 1997., 1997.3
    Searchable electronic edition of the first 49 volumes of
    , encoded in TEI-conformant SGML. Keyboarding by Remote Services, Portland, Oreg.; image scanning by Karen Wikander at the University of Virginia Electronic Text Center. Incorporates 1996.4.